<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Unit Converter Lite</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">Unit Converter Lite is a free mobile application developed by Lite Mobile Tools. This Privacy Policy explains how information is handled when you use our app.\n\nBy installing or using Unit Converter Lite, you agree to the terms described in this Privacy Policy.\n\n**Information Collection and Use**\n\nUnit Converter Lite is designed to work primarily offline and does not require any registration. You can install the app and immediately start using it without creating an account.\n\n🔒 We do NOT collect, store, or share any personal information.\n\nSpecifically:\n\n * We do not collect names, email addresses, phone numbers, or any personal identifiers.\n * We do not require users to register or create an account.\n * We do not collect location data, usage analytics, or device information.\n * We do not use cookies or tracking technologies.\n\n**Offline Functionality**\n\nMost features of Unit Converter Lite, including length, weight, temperature, area, and speed conversions, work completely offline. All calculations are performed locally on your device. No data related to these calculations is transmitted to our servers or any third party.\n\n**Currency Conversion and Internet Usage**\n\nThe currency conversion feature may require an internet connection to retrieve the latest exchange rates from our secure API service. This connection is used only to update currency values.\n\n * No personal data is collected or transmitted during this process.\n * We do not store or log user requests.\n * Exchange rate updates are used solely to provide accurate conversion results.\n\nPlease note that standard network communication may involve technical data such as IP address handled by your internet service provider. This information is not collected or stored by Lite Mobile Tools.\n\n**Sharing of Information**\n\nSince we do not collect any user data, we do not sell, trade, rent, or share information with third parties.\n\n**Third-Party Services**\n\nUnit Converter Lite does not use third-party advertising SDKs, analytics tools, or tracking services that collect personal data.\n\n**Children’s Privacy**\n\nUnit Converter Lite does not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. As no personal data is collected from any users, the app is safe for general audiences.\n\n**Data Security**\n\nBecause we do not collect or store personal data, risks related to data breaches are minimized. We are committed to maintaining secure communication when retrieving currency exchange rates.\n\n**Changes to This Privacy Policy**\n\nLite Mobile Tools may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be reflected within the app with an updated revision date. Users are encouraged to review this policy periodically.\n\n**Your Acceptance of This Policy**\n\nBy installing and using Unit Converter Lite, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please discontinue use of the app.\n\nThis document was last updated on Feb, 2026.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_url">https://litemobiletools.blogspot.com/p/privacy-policy-for-unit-converter-lite.html</string>
</resources>